[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '呼びます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Розмова, діалог"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '話します' read in word?",
        "answer": "Показувати"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '話し' read in word?",
        "answer": "Починати"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji '見せます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Пояснювати, повідомляти"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '始めます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Адреса"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '教えます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Йти (опади)"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '住所' read in word?",
        "answer": "Ім*я"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '降ります' read in word?",
        "answer": "Одразу"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji '名前' read in word?",
        "answer": "Сіль"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '直ぐ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Цукор"
    }
]
